http://www.meproductions.com/privacy-policy.php

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is vital to our long-term relationship with you, and protecting your privacy is just one part of our mission to provide you with highly personalized and valuable service. In addition, in an effort to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will not knowingly collect personally identifying information from children under the age of 13. This statement describes our Standard Privacy Policy What Information is Collected; How Information is Collected; and by Whom is Information Collected Required Personally Identifiable Information To submit the forms on our Web site, you must enter your name and e-mail address etc. This required personally identifiable information is necessary for us to process transactions for you and contact you. General Information We collect general information about you when you visit our web site. This information includes technical information related to your computer and the manner in which you are accessing our site and includes such information as the internet protocol (IP) address of your computer, what operating system your computer is using, what browser software (e.g., Explorer, Netscape or other) your computer is using, and who your Internet service provider is, the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the web site from which you just came and the URL to which you go next and certain operating metrics, such as the amount of time you use our Web site. The general information that we gather about you may be aggregated with general information of all users to help us better understand how our site is used. In addition, we aggregate the general information and the personal information. We compile and analyze this aggregated information so that we can provide more meaningful information to corporate partners and more relevant content and advertisements to you. The Sharing of Collected Information Personally Identifiable Information We will not share your personally identifying information with other third parties without your consent, except for the following limited purposes: We are compelled to do so by law or by an order of a court or governmental authority. In order to cooperate with law enforcement authorities or governmental regulatory bodies. As we deem necessary to protect our rights, safety or property, our users or others to enforce our terms of use agreement or Standard Privacy Policy. Aggregated General Information In addition, we may share aggregated general information about our site with our partners or the general public. For example, we may share information regarding the daily number of unique users to our site with potential partners or others. Aggregated data does not contain any information that could be used to contact or identify you. Third Party Sites We may publish links to other sites from our web site. Please note that we do not control the content, practices or policies of any other site, including what information those sites collect about you. Accordingly, we do not endorse or hold ourselves responsible for the privacy policies or information gathering practices of any site that you may link to from our site. In addition, you may choose to respond to advertisements that are posted on our web site or made available via our service or to direct marketing offers from third party sponsors or advertisers. We do not control the content, practices or policies of our sponsors or advertisers and, accordingly, do not endorse or hold ourselves responsible for the privacy policies or information gathering practices of any sponsor or advertiser who may collect information about you. Amendments to Our Standard Privacy Policy We may, from time to time, amend our Standard Privacy Policy. If we do, then we will post such amendments to this document so that you may always have access to our most recent policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of our Standard Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time. If at any point we decide to disclose personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email. You will be given the choice at that time to "opt-out" of any disclosures of your personal information that you made available to us prior to the change in our policy. Acknowledgment and Acceptance of our Standard Privacy Policy When you use our site, you affirmatively agree to all terms of this Standard Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this Web site constitutes your continued agreement to the terms of the Terms, including this Standard Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of our Standard Privacy Policy, you should cease using our Web site.
Home
About
Clients
Press
Blog
Contact
DMC
Destination Management
South Florida 800.544.0033 | Central Florida 877.888.4436 | Email us at me@meproductions.com
Copyright © 2010 ME Productions. All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy
